RG 074:036, Lucius B. Barbour Genealogical Collection
Connecticut State Library
Lucius B. Barbour genealogical collection
circa 1900-1930
Connecticut State Library
Barbour, Lucius Barnes, 1878-1934
28 cubic feet (182 items)
Lucius B. Barbour (1878-1934) was appointed the first Public Records Examiner at the Connecticut State Library in 1911. The collection includes genealogical notes and abstracts from Connecticut vital, church, cemetery and probate records and from newspapers.
RG074_036
1973-004
Biographical Note
Lucius Barnes Barbour was born in Hartford on February 1, 1878 to General Lucius A. and Harriet Barnes Barbour. He graduated from Hartford Public High School in 1896 and from Yale University in 1900. He married Charlotte Cordelia Hilliard of Hartford and they had a son and a daughter. He died at his summer home in Fenwick on July 29, 1934.
In 1911, Barbour was appointed the first Examiner of Public Records as assistant to the State Librarian, a position he held until his death. He was captain of Company K in 1916 and trained his company when it was mobilized for service at the Mexican border. He took ill before the troops left for the border and his physicians refused to certify him as fit for active service and he resigned his command. Barbour went to Washington in 1917 to serve on the provost marshal's staff for fifteen months. He was a major of the First Company, Governor's Foot Guard in 1920. He was quartermaster general with the rank of brigadier general on the staff of Governor Lake.
Barbour belonged to several organizations including the Acorn Club of Connecticut, the Farmington Country Club, the Fenwick Golf Club, the Hartford Club, Connecticut Society Founders and Patriots of America, Military Order of Foreign Wars, Sphinx Temple, AAONMS, the Society of Colonial Wars, Jeremiah Wadsworth Chapter of the Sons of the American Revolution, the Twentieth Century Club, Yale Alumni Association, Connecticut Historical Society, and the Hartford Oratorio Society.
Source: "Col. Barbour Dies Aged 56 in Fenwick." Hartford Courant, 1934 July 30, 1.
Scope and Content
The collection includes genealogical notes and abstracts from Connecticut vital, church, cemetery and probate records and from newspapers. Items directly related to the Barbour/Barber and Hilliard families are 8, 9, 10, 87, 88, 143, 144, 145, 146, 147, 150, 151, 175, 176, 180.
Related Material
None.
Index Terms
Persons:
Barbour, Lucius Barnes, 1878-1934; Belden, Joshua, 1768-1808; Hallock, Jeremiah, d. 1826; Grant, Matthew, 1601-1681; Bates, Albert Carlos, b. 1865; Larned, Ellen D. (Ellen Douglas), 1825-1912; Leavitt, Nason W; Williams, S. Maria; Hoadly, Charles J. (Charles Jeremy), 1828-1900; Canfield, Philemon, 1786-1864; Barbour, Harriet Elizabeth Barnes
Family Names:
Barnes family; Barber family; Brewster family; Burt family; Colton family; Cooley family; Case family; Day family; Clark family; Hart family; Dart family; Shaller family; Fitch family; Howlett family; Jordon family; Marsh family; Scarborough family; Smith family; Stibbins family; Bliss family; Hitchcock family; Hilliard family; Bulkeley family; Drake family; Ely family
Subjects:
Ashford (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Ashford (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Ashford; Barkhamsted (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Barkhamsted (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Bolton (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Bolton (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Vernon (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Bozrah (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Bozrah (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Bozrah; Branford (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Branford (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Branford (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Brooklyn (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Brooklyn (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Brooklyn; Columbia (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Columbia (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Columbia; Connecticut -- Genealogy; Society of Colonial wars in the State of Connecticut; Glastonbury (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Glastonbury; Glastonbury (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Eastford (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Eastford; Eastford (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; East Granby (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- East Granby; East Granby (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; East Hartford (Conn.) -- Genealogy; East Hartford (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; East Hartford (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Enfield (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Somers (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Enfield (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Somers (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Enfield; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Somers; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Franklin; Franklin (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Franklin (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Griswold (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Griswold; Griswold (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Hampton (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Hampton (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Hampton; Hartford (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; West Hartford (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Hartford; Hartford (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Harwinton (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Harwinton (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Harwinton (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Killingly (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Killingly (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Killingly; Lebanon (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Lebanon (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Lebanon; Lisbon (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Lisbon (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Lisbon; Lyme (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Lyme (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Lyme (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Middletown (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Middletown (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Middletown (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Montville (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Montville (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Montville; New Britain (Conn.) -- Genealogy; New Britain (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- New Britain; New Hartford (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; New Hartford (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- New Hartford; New London (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; New London (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- New London; Newington (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Newington (Conn.) --History -- Sources; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Newington; North Stonington (Conn.) -- Genealogy; North Stonington (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- North Stonington; Norwich (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Norwich (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Norwich; Plainfield (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Plainfield (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Plainfield; Pomfret (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Pomfret (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Pomfret; Preston (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Preston (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Preston; Rocky Hill (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Rocky Hill (Conn.) -- History -- sources; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Rocky Hill; Roxbury (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Roxbury (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Roxbury; Saybrook (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Saybrook (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Saybrook (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Simsbury (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Simsbury (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Bloomfield (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Simsbury (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Simsbury; Somers (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Somers (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Killingly (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Killingly (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Killingly; Sprague (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Sprague (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Sprague; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Stonington; Stonington (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Stonington (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Suffield (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Suffield (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Thompson (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Thompson (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Tolland (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Tolland (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Tolland (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Vernon (Conn.) -- History --Sources; Vernon (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Vernon; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Voluntown; Voluntown (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Voluntown (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- West Hartford; West Hartford (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; West Hartford (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Wethersfield (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Wethersfield (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- West Hartford; Windsor (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Epitaphs -- Connecticut -- Windsor; Epitaphs -- Connecticut -- Bloomfield; Cemeteries -- Connecticut -- Bloomfield; Cemeteries -- Connecticut -- Windsor; Windsor (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Wintonbury Cemetery (Bloomfield, Conn.); East Windsor Cemetery (Conn.); Poquonock Cemetery (Windsor, Conn.); Windsor Cemetery (Conn.); Windsor (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Windsor; Bloomfield (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Cemetery records and registers -- Connecticut -- Bloomfield; Woodstock (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Woodstock (Conn.) -- History -- Sources; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- Woodstock; Church records and registers -- Connecticut -- East Windsor; East Windsor (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Probate records -- Connecticut; Probate records -- Connecticut -- Brooklyn; Probate records -- Massachusetts -- Plymouth County; Plymouth County (Mass.) -- Genealogy; Probate records -- Connecticut -- East Hartford; Probate records -- Connecticut -- Glastonbury; Probate records -- Connecticut -- East Windsor; Probate records -- Connecticut -- Hartford; Probate records -- Connecticut -- Pomfret; Probate records -- Connecticut -- Suffield; Probate records -- Connecticut -- Windsor; Probate records -- Connecticut -- Wethersfield; Windham (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Probate records -- Connecticut -- Windham; Probate records -- Connecticut -- Woodstock; Plymouth (Mass.) -- Genealogy; Massachusetts -- Genealogy; Pennsylvania -- Genealogy; Registers of births, etc. -- Connecticut; Connecticut -- Statistics, Vital; East Haddam (Conn.) -- Genealogy; East Haddam (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; New Haven (Conn.) -- Genealogy; New Haven (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Norwich (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Springfield (Mass.) -- Genealogy; Springfield (Mass.) -- Statistics, Vital; Westfield (Mass.) -- Genealogy; Westfield (Mass.) -- Statistics, Vital; Mansfield (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Mansfield (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Chatham (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Chatham (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Cheshire (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Cheshire (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Massachusetts -- Statistics, Vital; East Hampton (Conn.) -- Genealogy; East Hampton (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; East5 Windsor (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Glastonbury (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Hartford (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Southington (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Burlington (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Goshen (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Southington (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Burlington (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Goshen (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; New Hartford (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Suffield (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Wethersfield (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Woodstock (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Barbour, Lucius Albert, b. 1846; Hilliard, Charlotte Cordelia; Hilliard, Elisha Earnest; Cemeteries -- Connecticut -- Hartford; Old North Cemetery (Hartford, Conn.); Old Saybrook (Conn.) -- genealogy; Ancient Burying Ground (Hartford, Conn.); Old South Burying Ground (Hartford, Conn.); Bethlehem (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Cemeteries -- Connecticut -- Bethlehem; Cemeteries -- Connecticut -- Roxbury; Cemeteries -- Connecticut -- Southbury; Southbury (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Washington (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Cemeteries -- Connecticut -- Washington; Woodbury (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Cemeteries -- Connecticut -- Woodbury; First Church of Christ (Hartford, Conn.); Canton (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Westerly (R.I.) -- History -- Sources; Westerly (R.I.) -- Genealogy; Westerly (R.I.) -- Statistics, Vital; Sterling (Conn.) -- Genealogy; Plainfield (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Sterling (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Voluntown (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital; Cemeteries -- Massachusetts -- Sandisfield; Sandisfield (Mass.) -- Genealogy
Document Types:
Clippings; Genealogies; Notebooks
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Collection, circa 1900-1930
  - Genealogical notes compiled from Ashford church records: admissions, baptisms, marriages, and deaths, 1760-1817, 1 volume (Box 1, Volume 1)
    Abstract of vital records.
    Arranged alphabetically.
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Barkhamsted, Conn. 1769-1818, 1 volume (Box 1, Volume 2)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from records of Bolton and Vernon, Conn. 1724-1860, 2 volumes (Box 1, Volume 3)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of New Concord and Norwich Fourth Society, Bozrah, Conn. 1739-1813, 1 volume (Box 1, Volume 4)
  - Abstract of Branford, Conn. vital statistics, 1658-1786, 1920; 1 volume (2 copies) (Box 1, Volume 5)
    Abstract of church vital records.
    Arranged chronologically.
  - Genealogical notes compiled from the Mortlake Church, Brooklyn, Conn. 1734-1824, 1 volume (Box 1, Volume 6)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Lebanon Crank and Lebanon Second Society, Columbia, Conn. 1720-1836, 1 volume (Box 1, Volume 7)
  - Genealogy of Lucius Barnes Barbour and his wife Charlotte Cordelia Hilliard. 1642-1800, 1 volume (Box 2, Volume 8)
  - Lineages of the ancestors of Lucius A. Barbour and Harriet Elizabeth Barnes. 1603-1849, 2 volumes (Box 1, Volume 9-10)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from records of the Connecticut Society of Colonial Wars. 1593-1916, 2 volumes (Box 2, Volume 11)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Durham, Conn. 1699-1820, 1 volume (Box 1, Volume 12)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Glastonbury, Conn. 1770-1848, 1 volume (Box 2, Volume 13)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Eastford, Conn. 1766-1804, 1 volume (Box 2, Volume 14)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from Turkey Hills church records, East Granby, Conn. 1643-1848, 1 volume (Box 2, Volume 15)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from records of East Hartford, Conn. 1748-1800, 1 volume (1255 p.) (Box 2, Volume 16)
    Abstract of baptisms.
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of East Hartford, Conn.: Abbey-Barnard families. 1646-1870, 1 volume (Box 2, Volume 17)
    Abstract of East Hartford church records.
  - Genealogical notes compiled from town and church records of Enfield, Conn. 1682-1800 and Somers, Conn., 1730-1750. 1682-1800, 2 volumes (Box 3, Volume 18)
    Arranged alphabetically. Volume 1: A-L; Volume 2: M-Z.
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of West Farms and Second Society of Norwich, Franklin, Conn. 1719-1852, 1 volume (Box 3, Volume 19)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Griswold, Conn. 1720-1809, 1 volume (Box 3, Volume 20)
    Church established as Preston Second Society
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Groton, Conn. 1727-1811, 1 volume (Box 3, Volume 21)
    First society.
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Canada Parish and Windham Second Society, Hampton, Conn. 1723-1824, 1 volume (Box 3, Volume 22)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Hartford and West Hartford, Conn. 1670-1821, 1 volume (Box 3, Volume 23)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from vital statistics of Hartford land records vols. 2, 3 & 5. 1660-1800, 1 volume (67 p.) (Box 3, Volume 24)
    Abstract of vital records of Hartford land records.
  - Genealogical notes compiled from Connecticut newspapers. 1775-1830, 1 volume (Box 4, Volume 25)
    Abstract of miscellaneous genealogical information of Conn.
  - Genealogical notes compiled from records of Harwinton, Conn. 1737-1790, 1 volume (Box 3, Volume 26)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Killingly, Conn. 1715-1816, 1 volume (Box 3, Volume 27)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Lebanon, Conn. 1729-1822, 1 volume (Box 4, Volume 28)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Lebanon Street and Lebanon First Society, Lebanon, Conn. 1701-1821, 1 volume (Box 4, Volume 29)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Newent and Norwich Third Society, Lisbon, Conn. 1723-1803, 1 volume (Box 4, Volume 30)
  - Early families of Lyme [Conn.] 1715-1845, 1 volume (Box 4, Volume 31)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from town records of Middletown, Conn. 1662-1833, 4 volumes (Box 4-5, Volume 32)
    Volumes 1 & 2 are in Box 4; Volumes 3 (J-R)& 4 (M-Z) are in Box 5.
  - Genealogical notes compiled from early Middletown families. 1652-1753, 1 volume (Box 5, Volume 33)
    Abstract of early Middletown families.
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Montville, Conn. 1722-1785, 1 volume (Box 5, Volume 34)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of New Britain, Conn. 1680-1850, 1 volume (Box 5, Volume 35)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of New Hartford, Conn. 1697-1827, 1 volume (Box 5, Volume 36)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of New London, Conn. 1671-1821, 1 volume (Box 5, Volume 37)
  - The first records of the Congregational Church in Newington, Conn. 1747-1805, marriages, baptisms, deaths as kept by Rev. J. Belden, pastor of the church, 1906; 1 volume, typescript (Box 5, Volume 38)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of North Stonington, Conn. 1727-1822, 1 volume (Box 5, Volume 39)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Norwichtown and Norwich First Society, Norwich, Conn. 1700-1832, 1 volume (Box 6, Volume 40)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from the Chelsea or Norwich Sixth Society of Norwich, Second Church, Norwich, Conn. 1760-1831, 1 volume (Box 6, Volume 41)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Christ Episcopal Church, Norwich, Conn. 1768-1844, 1 volume (Box 6, Volume 42)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Plainfield First Society, Plainfield, Conn. 1747-1819, 1 volume (Box 6, Volume 43)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Pomfret and Abington Societies, Pomfret, Conn. 1716-1825, 1 volume (Box 6, Volume 44)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Preston First Society, Preston, Conn. 1698-1827, 1 volume (Box 6, Volume 45)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Rocky Hill, Conn. 1765-1856, 1 volume (Box 6, Volume 46)
    Abstract of vital records of Rocky Hill (Stepney) Church.
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Roxbury, Conn. 1643-1688, 1 volume (Box 6, Volume 47)
  - Transcripts of vital statistics taken from the Saybrook town records, 1643-1835 and from the Saybrook probate records, 1780-1835, Hartford, Connecticut State Library, 1912, 1 volume, photostat of typescript copy (Box 6, Volume 48)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from Stebbins family record of Simsbury and inscriptions from St. Andrews Cemetery, Bloomfield, Conn. 1719-1827, 1 volume, photostat of typescript copy (Box 6, Volume 49)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from town and church records of Simsbury, Conn. 1666-1875, 1 volume (Box 7, Volume 50)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from records of Somers, Conn. 1647-1880, 1 volume (Box 6, Volume 51)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of South Killingly, Conn. 1745-1825, 1 volume (Box 6, Volume 52)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from records of the church in Hanover, the Eighth Society of Norwich, organized 1768, incorporated 1761, Sprague, Conn. 1768-1832, 1 volume (Box 6, Volume 53)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Stonington, Conn. 1675-1866, 1 volume (Box 6, Volume 54)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from records of Suffield, Conn. 1641-1898, 2 volumes (Box 8, Volume 55)
    Arranged alphabetically. Part 1: A-K, Part 2: L-Z.
  - Genealogical notes compiled from records of Thompson Parish and Killingly Second Society, Thompson, Conn. 1730-1795, 1 volume (Box 6, Volume 56)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from records of Tolland, Conn. 1716-1847, 1 volume (Box 7, Volume 57)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Vernon, Conn. 1762-1818, 1 volume, typescript (Box 7, Volume 58)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Voluntown, Conn. 1723-1825, 1 volume (Box 7, Volume 59)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from West Hartford church records. 1683-1868, 1 volume (Box 7, Volume 60)
  - History of the church in West Simsbury Book II / by J. Hallock, pastor of said church. 1800-1851, 1 volume (Box 7, Volume 61)
    Abstract of church records of West Simsbury.
  - Genealogical notes compiled from records of Wethersfield, Conn. 1658-1848, 2 volumes (Box 7, Volume 62)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from records of the First Church of Wethersfield and other miscellaneous records. 1698-1835, 1 volume (500 pages) (Box 7, Volume 63)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from records of Wethersfield, Conn. 1692-1827, 1 volume (452 pages) (Box 8, Volume 64)
  - Some inscriptions in Ancient Windsor, Conn., circa 1915; 1 volume (452 pages) (Box 8, Volume 65)
    Contents: Windsor Cemetery; Poquonock Cemetery, Windsor; Wintonbury Cemetery, Bloomfield; East Windsor Cemetery.
  - Genealogical notes compiled from town records of Windsor, Conn. 1677-1850, 1 volume (Box 8, Volume 66)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from records of Windsor, Conn. 1637-1690, 1 volume (Box 8, Volume 67)
  - Matthew Grant's old church record, circa 1915; 1 volume, typescript (Box 8, Volume 68)
    Abstract of vital records copied from manuscript of A.C. Bates, Esq.
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Wintonbury, Conn. 1735-1840, 1 volume (Box 8, Volume 69)
    Abstract of vital records
  - Genealogical notes compiled from church records of Woodstock, Conn. 1692-1833, 1 volume (Box 8, Volume 70)
  - Index to East Windsor Church records. 1700-1820, card index (Box 26, Volume 71)
  - Abstract of probate records. 1740-1800, 1 volume (Box 8, Volume 72)
  - Abstract of Brooklyn probate records. 1786-1900, 1 volume (Box 8, Volume 73)
    Abstract of probate records
  - Abstract of probate records from Plymouth County, Massachusetts. 1686-1692, 1 volume (Box 9, Volume 74)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from East Hartford and Glastonbury probate records. 1800-1830, 1 volume (Box 9, Volume 75)
  - Abstracts of probate records from East Windsor, Conn. 1782-1800, 1 volume (Box 9, Volume 76)
  - Genealogical notes compiled from Hartford, Connecticut district probate records. 1751-1800, 1 volume (Box 9, Volume 77)
    Arranged by town.
  - Genealogical notes compiled from Hartford, Conn. probate records. circa 1820, 1 volume (Box 9, Volume 78)
  - Index to Hartford probate records, volumes 16-25 and East Windsor probate records, volumes 1-2. 1751-1800, 1 volume (Box 9, Volume 79)
    Index arranged by towns.
  - Index to Hartford probate records. 1751-1800, 1 volume (Box 9, Volume 80)